Guide to the Stephen Henry Schneider Papers SC1053
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Teaching and Professional Work, Series 8
  - Administrative files
    - Provost Memo "Energy Use, Climate Change & the Protection of Biodiversity", 2000 (Box 179, Folder 24)
    - Climate of the 20th Century - World Meteorological Organization C20, 1999-2000s (Box 179, Folder 25)
    - IIS (Institute for International Studies) Research Council Meeting 4-5:30 Red Room, 1996 (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - Environment + Security Task Force: Meetings - Galvez House Conference Room, 1996-1997 (Box 179, Folder 27)
    - IIS (Institute for International Studies) Research leaders froup (research and program issues), 1996-1997 (Box 179, Folder 28)
    - SRES (Special Report on Emissions Scenarios) Meeting, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 29)
    - IIS (Institute for International Studies) Honors - Focus Re-Authorization Request Validations, 1996 Sept (Box 179, Folder 30)
    - IIS (Institute for International Studies) Executive Committee Red Room 6-8pm, 1996 September 30 (Box 179, Folder 31)
    - Environmental Security - CISAC (Center for Inernational Security and Cooperation) - 2pm, 1996 October 30 (Box 179, Folder 32)
    - Prof. Julian Simon controversy, 1994 (Box 247, Item 24-27)
    - "The Study of Global Change" article and diagram, 1992 (Box 247, Folder 28)
    - contracts, 1979-1983 (Box 247, Folder 29)
    - Provost's Committee on Environmental Science, Technology & Policy (Donald Kennedy corresp.), Oct. 4, 1999 (Box 247, Folder 30)
    - SLAC cosmic ray project, 2003 (Box 247, Folder 31)
  - Consulting
    - Robert Ayres Environmental Effects of Nuclear Weapons Vol 1, Vol 2 (bound together), December 1965 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Conservation Biology (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Review for Jim Titus, 1993-1994 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - J. E. Kutzbach - Pangaean Climates: Megamonsoons of the Megacontinent, November 1988 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Senator Tim Wirth - articles and notes, 1989 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Stella Melugin Coakley, 1988 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    - Robert Yuhnke - Beijing Review Article, Feb 1989 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Dewey McLean - The Global Environmental Protection Act of 1988: Joint Hearings, September 1988 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - J.R. Vallentyne - First Direction, Then Velocity (and others), January 1989 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - Kathryn J. Arbeit - Case Studies in Rural Electrification on the Tohono O'odham, Navajo and Hopi Tribal Nations, May 1998 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Conrad Choiniere - A Production Function Approach to the GDP - Temperature Relationship, May 2001 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - Roger Pielke - Turning the Big Knob (email), March 2001 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Edith Brown Weiss - Seasonal Climate Forecasts and Energy Management, December 1980 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    - Irene Smith - IEA Coal Research, November 1989 (Box 166, Folder 14)
    - Peter Laut - CO2 and Climate Change - Perspective for the Nordic Countries, October 1989 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    - Daniel Kammen: Sea Level Rise or Fall? - Quantifying the credibility of energy projections..., April 1996 (Box 166, Folder 16)
    - Scientists in the Media/George Will/Roger Revelle, September 1992 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    - Phillip Russell - Tropospheric Aerosol Radiative Forcing Observational Experiement, March 1996 (Box 166, Folder 18)
    - Nuclear Winter Articles (1/2) (Box 166, Folder 19)
    - Nuclear Winter Articles (2/2) (Box 166, Folder 20)
    - Climate Cloud Forest Stanford GRP, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 21)
    - Cloud Forest, 1995 (Box 166, Folder 22)
    - Cloud Forest Project, 1996 (Box 166, Folder 23)
    - Cloud Forest (Box 166, Folder 24)
    - Cloud Forest, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 25)
    - Climate Change Impacts on Tropical Moutane Cloud Forests (draft) (Box 166, Folder 26)
    - Cloud Forest GRP, 1997-98 (Box 166, Folder 27)
    - Climate Cloud Forest Stanford GRP, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 28)
    - SHS Environmental Modeling and Assessment proofs (ind. diskette) 3.5", January 1998 (Box 166, Folder 29)
    - EMA Proofs, November 1997 (Box 166, Folder 30)
    - EMA Process Comments (1/2), 1995-97 (Box 166, Folder 31)
    - EMA Process Comments (2/2), 1997 (Box 166, Folder 32)
    - EMA Process, 1997 (Box 166, Folder 33)
    - EMA8, September 1997 (Box 166, Folder 34)
    - EMA, May 1997 (Box 166, Folder 35)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1995-1998 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1997 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1998-2002 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 2000-2004 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Confronting Climate Change in California, November 1999 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    - Putting the Lid on Fossil Fuels - Greenpeace, March 1997 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Kyoto (notes, clippings, publications, corr), 1997-98 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Sponsored Projects - Rate Sheet/ Roceting Sheet - SU42, 1993-1995 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Sponsored Projects, 1995-1997 (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Discovery Channel, 1997 (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Fareed S. Fard Ahura Energy Inc., late 1990s-mid/late 2000s (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - MOORE Proposal (Hadly et al.), 2002 (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - SHS 60th birthday - cards, February 2005 (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Whole Earth Systems Conference - Integrating Environmental Science, Technology and Policy, February 2005 (Box 168, Folder 7)
    - PNAS Pending, 2005-2007 (Box 168, Folder 8)
    - Oxford Encyclopedia on Climate - Table of Contents, 2007 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    - PNAS Track Submission "Bleaching Susceptibility...coral reefs", 2007 (Box 168, Folder 10)
    - PNAS General Information, 2007 (Box 168, Folder 11)
    - PNAS Lenton et al. "Tipping Elements in the Earth System", 2007 (Box 168, Folder 12)
    - PNAS Elzen and Vuuren: Peaking Profiles for achieving long-term temperature targets with more likelihood at lower costs, 2007 (Box 168, Folder 13)
    - PNAS - Editing "The role of symbiont diversity in coral response to climate change" by Baskett; Gaines; Nisbet, 2007 (Box 168, Folder 14)
    - Cancer, 2007-2008 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    - Xavier Rodo - PNAS, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 16)
    - Schaeffer et al. Reducing Climate-Change Risk: Linear Returns to Costs, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 17)
    - Aldo Leopold Fellowship Program, November 2008 (Box 168, Folder 18)
    - IPER 310, Fall 2008 (Box 168, Folder 19)
    - Dying Planet, by Paul Brown - movie project manuscript with SHS edits, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 20)
    - Attribution of polar warming to human influence (SHS:Reviewer), 2008 (Box 168, Folder 21)
    - PNAS - Ganguly et al. "Higher trends bu larger uncertainty and geographic variability in 21st century temperature and heat waves" (Box 168, Folder 22)
    - The Power of Sustainable Thinking by Bob Doppett (SHS:Reviewer), 2008 (Box 168, Folder 23)
    - Cooler's "Lightening the Load" project, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 24)
    - Pizer; Snachirico "Regional patterns of U.S. Household Carbon Emissions" - track 1 Submission, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 25)
    - PNAS Rachel Warren "Avoiding Dangerous Anthropogenic Interference in Climate Change and Ecosystems", 2007-2008 (Box 168, Folder 26)
    - PNAS Seitz "Hydrols and Albedo: Microbubbles, Climate Change and Water Conservation", 2008 (Box 168, Folder 27)
    - PNAS track 1 submission: Funk, et al. The Warm Ocean, dry Africa dipole, 2007-2008 (Box 168, Folder 28)
    - PNAS Can Vuuren et al. - "Temperature increase of 21st Century Stabilization Scenarios, 2007-2008 (Box 168, Folder 29)
    - Padgham - "Migratory water birds reveal major influence of the Madden-Julian Oscilation on Arid Australian Ecosystems", 2008 (Box 168, Folder 30)
    - S. McMenamin PNAS - Climate Change and Wetland Desiccation Cause Amphibian Decline in World's Oldest National Park, 2008 (Box 168, Folder 31)
    - Journal Reviews, 1988-89 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Journal Reviews, 1990-96 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Ecological Economics Rev. "Climate Change and Ins. Indees.", September 1996 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Dennis Hartmann "Our Changing Climate: Reports to the Nation Series", September 1996 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Ecological Economics "Urgent Need to Internalize CO2 Emission Costs", May 1997 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Reviews Requested, 1989-1994 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - SHS as reviewer, 1992-1996 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - SHS as reviewer, 1990-1996 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - SHS as reviewer, 1990-1991 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - SHS as reviewer, 1990 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - SHS as reviewer, 1990 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - SHS as reviewer (proposals and articles) 1/2, 1988-1989 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - SHS as reviewer (proposals and articles) 2/2, 1988-1989 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - InstAAR - Institute of Arctic & Alpine Research 1/2, 1988-1989 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - InstAAR - Institute of Arctic & Alpine Research 2/2, 1989-1991 (Box 172, Folder 15)
    - Assoc. Editor of Conservation Biology, 1994 (Box 172, Folder 16)
    - Conservation Biology, 1994-1996 (Box 172, Folder 17)
    - Mitigation & Adaptation Strategies for Global Change review, 1999-2000 (Box 172, Folder 18)
    - Kluwer Academic Publishers - Atmospheric and Oceanographic Sciences, 1999 (Box 172, Folder 19)
    - Ed. Board - Martens, McMichale, Patz, 1999 (Box 172, Folder 20)
    - Rev. M. Miller Exploratorium, October 1997 (Box 172, Folder 21)
    - BBook Blurbs, Misc. (Box 172, Folder 22)
    - DWJTV - Nicki Johnson: Interview Transcript, 1996 July 16 (Box 179, Folder 33)
    - Scholastic's Magic School Bus (E.B. Fleishman), 1997 Jan 16 (Box 179, Folder 34)
    - Environmental Modelling & Assessment: Rotmans, Vrieze, Filar, eds. - Maastricht, 1996 Aug 26 (Box 179, Folder 35)
    - Long Term Global, 1992 (Box 179, Folder 36)
    - World Book Encyclopedia: Global Warming Article for 8th graders- 750 words (Jay, Myers, eds.), 1996 (Box 179, Folder 37)
    - "On the Front Lines of Climate Wars" - Michael Mann, 2010 (Box 179, Folder 38)
    - Cambridge "Science Communication for Scientists", 2010 August (Box 179, Folder 39)
    - National Geographic Explorers Symposium, 2010 (Box 179, Folder 40)
    - Witness Statement of Dr. Stephen Schneider - Auckland NZ, 2009 Sept (Box 179, Folder 41)
    - Senator Tim Wirth Senate Hearing (1988) & Energy Bill (1989), 1988-1989 (Box 179, Folder 42)
    - Sierra Club Publishing Agreement & Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 179, Folder 43)
    - NSF (National Science Foundation) Proposal - Biocomplexity Modeling, 2001 (Box 179, Folder 44)
    - Global Climate Change [SHS: Reviewer], 1990 (Box 179, Folder 45)
    - NCAR (National Center for Atmospheric Research) Research Outline & Budget Request, 1988 October (Box 179, Folder 46)
    - "Sudden & Disruptive Climate Change" by M. MacCraken - endorsements, blurbs, etc., 2007 (Box 179, Folder 47)
    - Robert Ubell Assoc. / Encyclopedia of Climate & Weather - memos, 1993-1994 (Box 179, Folder 48)
    - UC Santa Barbara School of Environmental Science & Management - interview for Dean's Position, 1993 (Box 179, Folder 49)
    - edited GAO (General Accounting Office) Audit Letter - George Miller, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 50)
    - The Luncheon Society, 2007 July 9 (Box 179, Folder 51)
    - Amicus brief, 2008 (Box 179, Folder 52)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists (Science + Security Board Business Meeting), 2009 Nov 5 (Box 179, Folder 53)
    - Unfiled Contracts and misc., 2007-2010 (Box 179, Folder 54)
    - The Fire Next Time: media production, 1992 (Box 179, Folder 55)
    - US Climate Action Network - edited press release, 1997 Oct 22 (Box 179, Folder 56)
    - Defining and Teaching Environmental Literacy - TREE vol. 12, no.11, 1997 Nov (Box 179, Folder 57)
    - BP Amoco, 1999-2000 (Box 179, Folder 58)
    - James Cohee [correspondence], ed. Sierra Club Books re: "Weather Permitting", 1981-1983 (Box 179, Folder 59)
    - Thames TV Ltd., 1982-1987 (Box 179, Folder 60)
    - Colorado Endowment for the Humanities 1/2 - Transcripts and proposals/prospectus for Nuclear Winter documentary with Cheryl Schneider and Don Kinney, 1985-1987 (Box 179, Folder 61)
    - Colorado Endowment for the Humanities Transcripts 2/2, 1985-1987 (Box 179, Folder 62)
    - Don Herbert / Mr. Wizard "How about...", 1986-1988 (Box 179, Folder 63)
    - Nuclear Winter - Ethics of Dispute: Colorado Endowment for the Humanities Transcripts, 1987-1988 (Box 179, Folder 64)
    - Point of View - Nuclear Winter Documentary, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 65)
    - Pastore, Rita PBS (Public Broadcasting Service) Series & Script Outline, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Kenneth Engel, 1980 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Bill Moyers, 1981 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Annenberg/ CPB (Corporation for Public Broadcasting) Project, 1983 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Linda.O. Mearns, et. al: Analysis of Climate Variability in GCM's (General Circulation Models), 1989 May (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - US Information Agency interview with Ecuador, 1989 Nov 28 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Panel on Policy Impl. of Greenhouse Warming (National Academy of Sciences) COSEPUP (Committee on Science, Engineering and Public Policy) - 1/2, 1989 Nov 13 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Panel on Poilcy Impl. of Greehouse Warming NAS - COSEPUP 2/2, 1989 Nov 13 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - African Journalists Symposium at NCAR (National Center for Atmospheric Research), 1990 March (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - Synthesis Panel (National Academy of Sciences) - Adaptation to Climate Change report - Seattle, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Synthesis Panel, 1990 Nov 23-24 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    - Synthesis Panel Mtg., 1990 Sept. 12-13 (Box 180, Folder 12)
    - Mitigation Panel - Policy Implications of Greenhouse Warming, 1990 July 10 (Box 180, Folder 13)
    - Synthesis Panel NAS (National Academy of Sciences) - Seattle, 1990 July 8-11 (Box 180, Folder 14)
    - After the Warming with James Burke, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 15)
    - Report of the Synthesis Panel - (NAS) National Academy of Sciences Panel on Policy IMplcations of Global Warming, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 16)
    - Policy Implication - Greenhouse Warming Synthesis Report, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 17)
    - The Fire Next Time - Jim Henerson, 1992 June (Box 180, Folder 18)
    - Discovery Channel - Ben Shaw, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 19)
    - Earth Island Institute, 1994 (Box 180, Folder 20)
    - Pew Scholars Meeting, 1993 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Ben-Gurion University - Mitrani Center, 1991-1993 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - Global Change Institute (GCI) 1/3, 1988 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Global Change Institute (GCI) 2/3, 1988 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Global Change Institute (GCI) 3/3, 1988 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Global Change Institute: Integrated Assessment of Climate Change - Snowmass, CO, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change pt. 1, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 7)
    - Committee on the Human Dimensions of Global Change pt. 2, 2000 (Box 181, Folder 8)
    - Status and Trends - Michael Mac - National Biological Survey/ Department of Interior 1/3, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 9)
    - Status and Trends - Michael Mac - National Biological Survey/ Department of Interior 2/3, 1994 (Box 181, Folder 10)
    - Status and Trends - Michael Mac - National Biological Survey/ Department of Interior 3/3, 1994-1997 (Box 181, Folder 11)
    - OECD (Organization for Economic Change and Development 1/3, 2002 Dec 13 (Box 181, Folder 12)
    - OECD (Organization for Economic Change and Development 2/3, 2002 Dec 13 (Box 181, Folder 13)
    - OECD (Organization for Economic Change and Development 3/3, 2002 Dec 13 (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Review copy of: Human Choice and Climate Change: An International Assessment - Rayner & Malone, eds. 1/2, 1997 (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - Review copy of: Human Choice and Climate Change: An International Assessment - Rayner & Malone, eds. 2/2, 1997 (Box 181, Folder 16)
    - Planet Earth scripts 1/3 (Box 181, Folder 17)
    - Planet Earth preview book 2/3, 1985 (Box 181, Folder 18)
    - Planet Earth telecourse and correspondence 3/3, 1984-1985 (Box 181, Folder 19)
    - Planet Earth - Fate and Climate panels - Los Angeles, San Diego, 1985 Aug (Box 181, Folder 20)
    - CBS: Fire Next Time, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 52)
    - Chevron video, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 53)
    - Coupled Human & Natural Systems, 2003 (Box 201, Folder 54)
    - Global Warming Prevention Act HR 5460 (1/2), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Global Warming Prevention Act HR 5460 (2/2), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Global Warming Prevention Act - Correspondence - Claudine Schneider, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Correspondence and list of testimony before Congress, 1989 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Correspondence - Margolin, Eckhardt, 1979-1991 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Al Gore, 1990-1996 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Clinton / Gore, 1992 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Tim Wirth, 1990-1992 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Tim Wirth, 1989-1990 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Tim Wirth, 1988-1996 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Senate Committee on Government Affairs, 1979 July (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - Project 88, 1988-1991 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - Wirth Energy Bill, 1988-1992 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - Dukakis Environment Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Science and Technology, 1981 July 31 (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - SHS Adelaide Thinkers in Residence - Australia (+ additional material - books, magazines, pamphlets), 2006 (Box 218, Folder 1-14)
    - Magic School Bus - proposal, 1991 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Magic School Bus, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Magic School Bus, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Magic School Bus, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Magic School Bus, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Magic School Bus, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Magic School Bus, 1996 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Magic School Bus, 1997 (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Magic School Bus - book, 1997 (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - NOVA: Stormchasers, 1995 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - NAS: Bruce Alberts - publications and correspondence, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - World Resources Institute: Teachers Guide, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 12)
    - USC Environmental Studies Program, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 13)
    - Blair, Robert: Project 2061, undated (Box 226, Folder 14)
    - Blair, Robert: Conservation Biology Text, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Blair, Robert: Conservation Biology Student Workbook, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 16)
    - Blair, Robert: California Guide to Environmental Literacy (draft), 1996 (Box 226, Folder 17)
    - California Science Education Advisory Committee: review standards, 1997 (Box 226, Folder 18)
    - Redfern, Ron: Earth Systems database (rejected), 1995 (Box 226, Folder 19)
    - GLOBE (Global Learning and Observation to Benefit the Environment) program: NSF & NOAA Education proposal, 1994 (Box 226, Folder 20)
    - San Francisco Estuary Project, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 21)
    - The Future of Climate: Potential for Interaction and Surprises (SHS), 1995 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - National Institute for Global Encironmental Change (NIGEC), 1995-1996 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - NIGEC, 1994-1996 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - NIGEC, 1993-1996 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - NTAC Meeting (NIGEC), 1996 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - NIGEC Board of Trustees - D.C., 1996 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - NIGEC Meeting, 1994 March (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - NIGEC Names/Fax/Addresses (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - NIGEC Board of Trustees - Phone Conference, 1995 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - NIGEC Correspondence, 1995 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - NIGEC Board of Trustees Conference - Oakland, 1994 (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - IGBP - International Geosphere-Biosphere Program, 1985-1989 (Box 244, Folder 12-14)
    - Status and Trends of the Nation's Biological Resources - Volume 1: Factors Affecting Biological Resources - Climate Change, 1997 (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - "Status and Trends" book chapter correspondence and edits, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - notes for SEJ (Society for Environmental Journalists) debate, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 17)
    - 11th hour follow-up and Common Wealth Club (San Francisco) (Box 244, Folder 18)
    - Magic School Bus Advisory Board, 1991-1998 (Box 244, Folder 19)
    - Nexus: The interaction of Science and Public Policy - public radio series, 1984-1985 (Box 244, Folder 20)
    - "After the Nuclear War" Japanese TV - Nippon Hoso Kyokai, 1984-1985 (Box 244, Folder 21)
    - NOVA "Goddess of the Earth", 1985-1986 (Box 244, Folder 22)
    - Global Climate Change digest ceases publication, 1999 November (Box 244, Folder 23)
    - Galileo Studies "Significant Hazards", 1984-1987 (Box 244, Folder 24)
    - John Brockman - correspondence and contracts - Science Masters, etc., 1988-1994 (Box 244, Folder 25)
    - Policy Implications of Greenhouse Warming Mitigation Report, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 26-28)
    - Mitigation Report version 4.0 - National Academy of Sciences, 1990 (Box 244, Folder 29)
    - National Academy of Sciences Synthesis Panel, 1989 (Box 244, Folder 30)
    - Comments, Commissions, Requests for Writing, 1977-1995 (Box 244, Folder 31)
    - Mr. Wizard, 1977-1981 (Box 244, Folder 32)
    - NatGeo: Forces of Nature, script & correspondence, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 32)
- Works by Others, Series 9
  - Alphabetical by author
    - Davis, Margaret Bryan (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - De Freitas, C.R. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Delacourt, Paul & Hazel (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Dickinson, Robert E. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Dietrich, David E. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Donn, William L. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Donnelly, Richard F. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Driscoll, Dennis M. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Druyan, L.M. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Dunlap, Riley E. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Duplessy, Jean Claude (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - D (da-Dill) (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - D (Dou-Dys) (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Easterling, William E. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Eddy, John A. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Elgin, Duane (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Ellasaesser, Hugh (Box 72, Item 17-18)
    - Eltahir, Elfaith A.B. (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Ehrlich, Paul (Box 72, Item 20-21)
    - Epstein, Samuel (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - E (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Falcon, Walter P. (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Fearnside, Philip M. (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Fitzjarrald, David R. (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Flohn, Hermann (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Folland, C.K. (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Forrester, Jay W. (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Fraedrich, Klaus (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Frakes, L.A. (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Fraser, P.J. (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Fritts, H.C. (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - F (Fae-Fis) (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - F (Fla-Fri) (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - F (Fru-Fung) (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Gaffen, Dian J. (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Gaffney, J.S. (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Gal-Chen, Tzvi (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Gallimore, Robert G. (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Gates, Lawrence W. (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - Ghan, Steven J. (Box 72, Folder 42)
    - Ghil, Michael (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - Gilman, Donald L. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Giorgi, Filippo (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Glantz, Michael H. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Glatzmaier, Gary A. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Gleick, Peter H. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Goreau, Thomas J. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Gornitz, Vivien (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Goulder, Lawrence (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Graf, Hans-Friedrich (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Gribbon, John (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Grinevald, Jacques (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Grubb, Michael (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - G (Ga-Gil) (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - G (Gle-Gou) (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - G (Gre-Gun) (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Hall, Charles A.S. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Hall, Darwin C. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Hall, D.O. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Hansen, James (Box 73, Item 19-20)